Email: spp9311@nyu.edu Phone: 1-847-345-4258

GitHub: github.com/StanPreschlack Website: stan-preschlack.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/stan-preschlack-49aa211b2

#### Stan Preschlack

# **Summary**

As a highly motivated computer science student at New York University, I have a strong foundation in programming, debugging, and testing. I have experience in software development using multiple programming languages and tools, including **Typescript**, **React**, **NextJS**, **VueJS**, **QwikJS**, **Google Cloud Platform**, **AWS**, **ExpressJS**, **Go**, **Rust**, **Python**, **Java**, **C**, and **Git**. Additionally, I am well-versed in Agile practices and have excellent problem-solving, communication, and design skills. My personal website and GitHub showcase some of my recent projects.

**Education** 

#### New York University Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences

2020 - 2024 (expected), Bachelors in Computer Science

### Beacon Academy

2016 - 2020, International Baccalaureate Diploma

# **Work History**

### |Sales Floor Associate, 2015 - 2020 at Uncle Dan's LLC

Provide a welcoming and helpful environment for all customers, ensuring that they can find the products that they need on the sales floor. Assist customers with a variety of different sales departments, such as shoes, climbing equipment, kayaks, winter clothing, and camping essentials. Help customers make transactions on cloud-based check-out software. Take inventory of products quarterly, and process new orders as they arrive at the store. Help fill online customer orders in-store.

## |Canvasser, March 2021 - May 2021 at Meridian Strategies

Responsible for engaging in outreach in New York City relating to COVID-19 awareness. Worked passing out information and resources relating to COVID-19 testing and vaccination and signed interested residents up for vaccination.

## |Coding Coach, 2021 - present at CodeSpeak Labs

Teach basic programming and web development to a wide age range at a number of schools in New York City. Engage with students to help work through challenges in a project based learning curriculum.